Ah, hello.
あ、こんにちは
This is great.
こうはいいっすね
It's white now.
白いよね、今は
Is that so?
そうですかね
Not outside at all.
全然、外でない
Oh, are you leaving?
あ、出る?
Let's go out and have some fun.
遊びに行ったりな
Go out for fun or go shopping.
遊びに行ったり、買い物したり
Go shopping.
買い物したり
That's that white.
それ、その白いな
This is white.
白いですね、これ
nice.
いいね
How old are you now?
今何歳なんだっけ?
I'm 18 years old.
18歳です
18 years old, young.
18歳、若いね
I'm a first year university student.
大学1年生です
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
I've only just entered.
まだ入ったばっかりだから
yes.
そう
Is school fun?
学校楽しいですか?
fun.
楽しい
fun?
楽しい?
Are you used to it?
慣れた?
I'm used to it.
慣れましたね
What do you enjoy?
どんなことが楽しい?
College life with normal friends.
普通の友達と大学生活
Did you make friends?
友達できた?
I made a friend.
友達できました
So, what kind of university life are you having?
そ っか、どんな大学生活をやってるの?
I study, and when there is an autumn break, I go out to eat.
勉強して、秋こまがあったらご飯食べたりしてます
Good, be youthful.
いいね、青春なれ
Do you have a part-time job?
バイトとかしてる?
I work part-time at a cafe.
バイトはカフェでバイトしてます
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Because it's cute.
かわいいからね
Are you popular at school?
学校でモテるでしょ?
That's not the case.
そんなことないです
Are you dating anyone?
付き合ってる人がいるの?
There isn't.
ないんですね
Isn't it?
い ないの?
yes.
はい
Have you ever dated before?
最後に付き合ったことあるでしょ?
I've dated him before.
付き合ったことあります
When is the last time?
最後はいつ?
That was when I was in high school.
高校の時ですね
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Are you not there?
そっからいないの?
He's not there.
そっからいないですね
Was your boyfriend at that time a bit naughty?
その時の彼氏とは、ちょっとそういうエッチなこととか?
I did.
しました
Did you do a lot?
結構した?
I agree.
そうですね
That's right.
そうなんだ
Does it take a long time to stand up after the last match?
最後に一致してから結構立つの?
It stands up quite well.
結構立ちます
I haven't done it at all.
全然してないです
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
It's a waste.
もったいないね
Don't you feel like having sex?
エッチしたくなったりしない?
sometimes.
たまに
sometimes?
た まに?
Will it be?
なる?
What do you do in such a case?
そういう時どうするの?
Ah, I'll hold back.
あ、我慢します
Oh, hold on?
あ、我慢?
yes.
はい
There isn't one.
いないね
Do you do it alone?
一人でしたりするの?
I also did it alone.
一人でしたりもしましたね
picture?
え?
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
Well, he's around his age.
まあ、お年頃だしね
I'm nervous because I'm doing a lot of things.
ちょっといろんなことしてるから緊張してます
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
Don't be nervous.
緊張しないでください
It's cute.
可愛いっすね
Your breasts are a bit big, aren't they?
ちょっとおっぱいが大きいよね?
That's not the case.
そんなことないです
picture?
え?
It's emphasized.
強調されてる
You're not nervous, are you?
緊張してないでしょ?
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
Even if he touches me, even if I ask him if it's ok, he still touches me.
体触っちゃったりしても、いいですかって言っても触っちゃってる
But.
けど
It has a beautiful shape.
綺 麗な形してるね
It's nostalgic.
懐かしいよ
It's intense.
激しいね
Look, like this.
ほら、こんな
intense.
激しい
That's interesting.
面白いね
Isn't this a little see-through?
なんかこれっすとちょっと透けてない?
Underneath the see-through?
透けてる下に?
that's right.
そうです
Look, is it hair?
ちょっとほら、お毛毛かな?
No, it's true.
いや、ほんとだ
That's amazing.
すごいね
I can see it.
見えてるよ
Your butt is beautiful too.
お尻も綺麗だね
It's pure white.
真っ白じゃん
Are you hiding it?
隠してるの?
nostalgic.
懐かしい
No, it's really beautiful.
いや、すごい綺麗だよ
That's really bad.
すごいやばいな
The tension is amazing.
張りがすごいよ
funny.
おもしろい
amazing.
すごい
fun.
楽しい
I don't like it
嫌だ
Yo.
よ
It's beautiful.
綺 麗だよ
nostalgic.
懐かしい
Something here.
なんかここに
amazing.
すごい
What do you do?
何をするの?
i don't know.
知らない
It's been a while.
久しぶりに
Let me spread the mango with both hands.
両手でマンゴー広げてみせて
That's naughty.
やらしい
Wash this?
洗濯してこれ?
That's it, right?
それなんでしょ?
I'll do it.
やらちゃう
amazing.
すごい
That's amazing.
すごいね
Where did you learn it?
どこで覚えたの?
That's amazing.
すごいね
good.
上手
I'm going to spit it out.
吐き飛んじゃう
pain
痛
stomach?
い?
I'm sorry.
ご めんね
My body is completely white
体真っ白だ
hey.
ね
It feels amazing though.
すごい 気持ちいいんだけど
You can move like that.
そんな 動けるんだ
Sorry.
ごめんね
Erotic.
エロい
That's a great waist.
すごい腰遣いだね
put your hands behind your back
後ろに手をつ
Stay.
いて
Heel your feet slowly.
ゆ っくり足をヒールしてください
Erotic.
エロい
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいい
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
That's amazing.
すごいよ
My shoulders are starting to feel a little flat.
ちょっと肩がペタペタになってきた
Push it up.
押し上げて
amazing.
すごい
Are your legs good?
足いい?
Can I put it on my breasts?
おっぱいにかけていい?
So beautiful.
すごい綺麗
sorry.
ごめん